# Jackie Dube

## **Junior Web Developer**

Kempton Park, Gauteng 1619 jackienomsa3@gmail.com 067 076 9436

View portfolio

I am a 26 year old African female currently in the telemarketing and sales industry. I am a hard worker, I pay attention to every detail and I always aim for the best result in any and every job I do because everything I do and achieve is a reflection of me. I have experience in the hospitality industry, the retail industry and sales, however I am interested in computer programming and I have acquired several web development and programming skills. I am a fast learner and I have come to realize that there is nothing I cannot do once I put my mind to it.

### Work Experience

### **Business Development Executive Public**

Sector Indaba - Kempton Park, Gauteng January 2018 to March 2020

My job involved telesales to government and private entities, booking accommodation, boardrooms and conference rooms, and also host the events

#### **Sales Assistant**

Outdoor Warehouse March 2016 to November 2017

#### **Waitress**

September 2014 to January 2015

### Packaging staff

LSG

November 2013 to July 2014

#### Education

Future flyers academy July 2015 to October 2015

Oxford Combined College

December 2013

## Skills

### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Python, Django, Flask, SQL (MySQL, PostgreSQL), HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Materialize <u>View portfolio</u>

### **GENERAL COMPUTER SKILLS**

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Outlook

Certifications/Licences

## **Drivers License Code 10**

September 2016 to September 2021 Code 10